cbincomesecrets.com 2011-12-04

# Privacy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Welcome toÂ CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ (the "Site").

Privacy online is important to users of our Site as we understand it should be, especially when carrying out business transactions.Â 

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to both users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without

doing business and Visitors who register in order to conduct business on the Site and make use of the various products and services offered byÂ CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

**What is "Personally Identifiable Information"**

When we refer to "Personally Identifiable Information we mean any information that identifies an individual or that can be used to contact or find an individual whether that be name, address, phone number, fax , email address, financial information, social security number or other government issued numbers, or credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information collected anonymously (in other words, information we collect without asking you to identify yourself (like surveys or opinions) or demographics we get from monitoring our web traffic.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected on your site?**

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form [and/or create a user name and password]. During registration you [are required to] give[s] contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.Â 

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site.

We may send you links to audio or video content, special offers, information about new features of our services or services of our strategic partners.Â 

Dot Com Directis the sole owner of the information collected on CBIncomeSecrets.com. Paypal collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.Â 

**Orders** Â 

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).Â 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. Paypal and Clickbank collects personally identifiable information from our users to process our credit card transactions.Â 

**What organizations are collecting the information?**

In addition to our in house collection of information, our third party service vendors (primarily for payment processing but may include others) may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not and can not control how these third parties use such information, but we do expect them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers plainly on their own websites. Some of these third parties may be middlemen that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and may not store, retain, or use the information given to them.Â 

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**

We use Personally Identifiable Information to further develop the Site, to enrich and enhance our service offerings, and to fulfill buying requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers to survey them or for purchase and sales opportunities on the Site or other information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to customer service inquiries, or to provide requested information.Â 

**Who do you share the information with?**

Personally Identifiable Information is not shared outside of our business beyond what is required by law or necessary to conduct business and or marketing. We may share demographic information about our Visitors and Authorized Customers with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We always offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us by clicking an opt out link or copying and pasting said link into your web browser.Â 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**

Personally Identifiable Information collected byÂ CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ is securely stored behind password protected areas and is not accessible to third parties or employees ofÂ CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ except for use as indicated above.Â 

What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?

Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us atÂ www.AskOurStaff.com

**Do You Use Cookies on the Site?**

Cookies are used for several reasons. We may use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the products or services they select. We also may use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For instance, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is sitting idle and otherwise unused for more than 10 minutes, we may automatically log the Authorized Customer off. Cookies are used to determine an active subscription to some areas of our site and will expire without payment thus barring access to said areas. Deleting the cookies we set for subscriptions may interfere with your ability to access your membership. Cookies do not store credit card information, only whether or not a subscription is paid current or not.Â 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.Â 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Dot Com Directat CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**How doesÂ  CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ use login information?**

CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze which browsers or software are being used so we can improve our level of service, administer the Site, track which areas show most interest by use, and gather broad demographic information.

What partners or other service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?

CBIncomeSecrets.comÂ has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors out of economic necessity and good business judgment.

Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility such as whether they can make a valid payment.

Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information as it is generally beyond our reasonable control. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law is a given. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information if requested. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.Â 

**Referrals** Â 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Dot Com Directdoes store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program].Â 

Your friend may contact us atÂ www.AskOurStaff.comÂ to request that we remove this information from our database.Â 

**What measures does the Site use to keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**

We make our employees familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is accessible to a limited number of employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We change our passwords to sensitive areas on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, are protected by third party encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, web based transactions and databases are subject to errors, tampering and hacking, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place nor will we be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such events.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Rasheed Ali atÂ www.AskOurStaff.comÂ .

**How can Visitors correct inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**

Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us atwww.AskOurStaff.comÂ 

**Can I as a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**

We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with an opt out mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database both included in emails we send or by contactingÂ www.AskOurStaff.com.Â However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information (and in fact it may be required by law to do so). An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted (in other words suspended from further contact), and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.Â 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications and you are a purchaser of our services, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us atwww.AskOurStaff.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of marketing communications by contacting us at 1-888-335-0883 to opt-out. Opting our of our newsletter and promotional communications will opt you out of any/all of our secondary offerings as well.

**How can I know if the Privacy Policy Changes?**

We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site (in this or other maintained and accessible pages).Â 

**Links to other sites:**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site which will be generally indicated by a change in domain name in your web browser. We recommend you read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
